Bottled with Love is a tv movie, romance film directed by David Weaver.
After being stood up, Abbey gets inspired to open her heart in a
letter, put it in a bottle and toss it out to sea.
Months later, a man fishing discovers it and opts to reach out.
Abbey Lawrence, played by Bethany Joy Lenz.
Nick Everson, played by Andrew W. Walker.
Sophie Everson, played by Kate Isaac.
Elaine, played by Bethany Brown.
Aunt Frances, played by Frances Flanagan.
George Wilmore, played by Everick Golding.
Andrew Walker  is a Canadian actor and film producer.
He made his film debut in Laserhawk (1997), followed by roles in American television
series such as Maybe It's Me, Sabrina the Teenage Witch, and Hot Properties.
He also co-starred in Steel Toes (2006), which earned him
an ACTRA Award for Best Actor in 2008.
He subsequently appeared in films such as The Mountie and The Gundown, and had
a starring role on the Lifetime cop drama Against the Wall.
The tone is emotional.